{
  "questions": [
    {"question": "Who made Runescape? (Jagex)", "answer": "Jagex", "type": "logic", "keyword": "Runescape"},
    {"question": "What colour is the sun?", "answer": "yellow", "type": "logic", "keyword": "sun"},
    {"question": "What colour is the sky?", "answer": "blue", "type": "logic", "keyword": "sky"},
    {"question": "What colour is the grass?", "answer": "green", "type": "logic", "keyword": "grass"},
    {"question": "What colour is the ocean?", "answer": "blue", "type": "logic", "keyword": "ocean"},
    {"question": "What colour is the moon?", "answer": "white", "type": "logic", "keyword": "moon"},
    {"question": "What colour is the snow?", "answer": "white", "type": "logic", "keyword": "snow"},
    {"question": "What pumps your blood?", "answer": "heart", "type": "logic", "keyword": "pumps"},
    {"question": "What colour is your blood?", "answer": "red", "type": "logic", "keyword": "blood"},
    {"question": "What colour is the fire?", "answer": "red", "type": "logic", "keyword": "fire"},
    {"question": "What colour is the leaf?", "answer": "green", "type": "logic", "keyword": "leaf"},
    {"question": "What colour is the apple?", "answer": "red", "type": "logic", "keyword": "apple"},
    {"question": "What colour are clouds?", "answer": "white", "type": "logic", "keyword": "clouds"},
    {"question": "What item tells the time?", "answer": "clock", "type": "logic", "keyword": "time"},
    {"question": "What shape is the letter 'O'?", "answer": "circle", "type": "logic", "keyword": "'O"},
    {"question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?", "answer": "square", "type": "logic", "keyword": "equal sides"},
    {"question": "What shape has 3 sides?", "answer": "triangle", "type": "logic", "keyword": "& sides"},
    {"question": "Can you lick you elbow?", "answer": "No", "type": "logic", "keyword": "elbow"},
    {"question": "What animal says 'oink'?", "answer": "pig", "type": "logic", "keyword": "oink"},
    {"question": "What animal says 'moo'?", "answer": "cow", "type": "logic", "keyword": "moo"},
    {"question": "What letter comes after h in the alphabet?", "answer": "i", "type": "logic", "keyword": "after h"},
    {"question": "What letter comes after r in the alphabet?", "answer": "s", "type": "logic", "keyword": "after r"},
    {"question": "What is the 5th letter of the word Pokemon?", "answer": "m", "type": "find", "keyword": "Pokemon"},
    {"question": "What is the 3rd letter of the word Armadyl?", "answer": "m", "type": "find", "keyword": "dyl"},
    {"question": "What is the third letter of the word stalls?", "answer": "a", "type": "find", "keyword": "stalls"},
    {"question": "What place is home of Ikov", "answer": "edgeville", "type": "find", "keyword": "home of Ikov"},
    {"question": "Spell Ikov backwards", "answer": "edgeville", "type": "voki", "keyword": "backwards"},
    {"question": "What is the 2nd letter of the word Runescape?", "answer": "u", "type": "find", "keyword": "word Runescape"},
    {"question": "How many letters are in the word Runescape?", "answer": "9", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "letters"},
    {"question": "How many letters are in the word Ikov?", "answer": "4", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "Ikov"},
    {"question": "How many servers are better than Ikov?", "answer": "0", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "servers"},
    {"question": "What is the name of this server? (Ikov)", "answer": "Ikov", "type": "logic", "keyword": "server"},
    {"question": "How many letters are in the word Friend?", "answer": "6", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "Friend"},
    {"question": "What do you pour with your cereal?", "answer": "milk", "type": "logic", "keyword": "cereal"},
    {"question": "What colour is the report abuse button?", "answer": "red", "type": "logic", "keyword": "abuse"},
    {"question": "What is one hundred in numbers?", "answer": "100", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "hundred"},
    {"question": "What piece of cutlery do you eat your soup with?", "answer": "spoon", "type": "logic", "keyword": "eat"},
    {"question": "How much is 5 + 15?", "answer": "20", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "15"},
    {"question": "If you have 89 and take 19 whats left?", "answer": "70", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "89"},
    {"question": "How much is 75 + 5?", "answer": "80", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "75"},
    {"question": "If you have 43 and add 14 what do you have?", "answer": "57", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "43"},
    {"question": "How much is 57 take 12 whats left?", "answer": "45", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "57"},
    {"question": "What is 84 + 12?", "answer": "96", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "84"},
    {"question": "What is 10 / 2?", "answer": "5", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "10"},
    {"question": "How much is 11 * 3?", "answer": "33", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "* 8?"},
    {"question": "What number comes before 4?", "answer": "3", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "before 4"},
    {"question": "What number comes after 4?", "answer": "5", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "after 4"},
    {"question": "What number comes before 8?", "answer": "7", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "before 8"},
    {"question": "What number comes after 8?", "answer": "9", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "after 8"},
    {"question": "How many eyes do you have?", "answer": "2", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "eyes"},
    {"question": "How many toes do you have?", "answer": "10", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "toes"},
    {"question": "How many thumbs do you have?", "answer": "2", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "thumbs"},
    {"question": "What does water freeze into?", "answer": "ice", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "water"},
    {"question": "What does ice melt into?", "answer": "water", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "ice"},
    {"question": "Defence levels for barrows?", "answer": "70", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "barrows"},
    {"question": "Defence levels for dragon?", "answer": "60", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "dragon"},
    {"question": "Defence levels for rune?", "answer": "40", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "rune"},
    {"question": "What colour is runite?", "answer": "blue", "type": "logic", "keyword": "runite"},
    {"question": "How many laws to cast teleblock?", "answer": "1", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "laws"},
    {"question": "How many fire runes to cast high alchemy?", "answer": "5", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "fire rune"},
    {"question": "How many inventory slots do you have?", "answer": "28", "type": "numeric", "keyword": "slots"},
    {"question": "What skill does the sword represent?", "answer": "attack", "type": "skills", "keyword": "sword"},
    {"question": "What skill does the fist represent?", "answer": "strength", "type": "skills", "keyword": "fist"},
    {"question": "What skill does the shield represent?", "answer": "defence", "type": "skills", "keyword": "shield"},
    {"question": "What skill does the bow represent?", "answer": "ranged", "type": "skills", "keyword": "bow"},
    {"question": "What skill does the star represent?", "answer": "magic", "type": "skills", "keyword": "star"},
    {"question": "What skill does the wizard hat represent?", "answer": "magic", "type": "skills", "keyword": "wizard"},
    {"question": "What skill does the saw represent?", "answer": "construction", "type": "skills", "keyword": "saw"},
    {"question": "What skill does the plank represent?", "answer": "construction", "type": "skills", "keyword": "plank"},
    {"question": "What skill does the ring represent?", "answer": "dungeoneering", "type": "skills", "keyword": "ring"},
    {"question": "What skill does the heart represent?", "answer": "hitpoints", "type": "skills", "keyword": "heart"},
    {"question": "What skill does the person represent?", "answer": "agility", "type": "skills", "keyword": "person"},
    {"question": "What skill does running represent?", "answer": "agility", "type": "skills", "keyword": "running"},
    {"question": "What skill does the herb represent?", "answer": "herblore", "type": "skills", "keyword": "herb"},
    {"question": "What skill does the mask represent?", "answer": "thieving", "type": "skills", "keyword": "mask"},
    {"question": "What skill does the chisel represent?", "answer": "crafting", "type": "skills", "keyword": "chisel"},
    {"question": "What skill does the hammer represent?", "answer": "crafting", "type": "skills", "keyword": "hammer"},
    {"question": "What skill does the arrow represent?", "answer": "fletching", "type": "skills", "keyword": "arrow"},
    {"question": "What skill does the skull represent?", "answer": "slayer", "type": "skills", "keyword": "skull"},
    {"question": "What skill does the paw represent?", "answer": "hunter", "type": "skills", "keyword": "paw"},
    {"question": "What skill does the print represent?", "answer": "hunter", "type": "skills", "keyword": "print"},
    {"question": "What skill does the pickaxe represent?", "answer": "mining", "type": "skills", "keyword": "pickaxe"},
    {"question": "What skill does the anvil represent?", "answer": "smithing", "type": "skills", "keyword": "anvil"},
    {"question": "What skill does the fish represent?", "answer": "fishing", "type": "skills", "keyword": "fish"},
    {"question": "What skill does the pot represent?", "answer": "cooking", "type": "skills", "keyword": "pot"},
    {"question": "What skill does the fire represent?", "answer": "firemaking", "type": "skills", "keyword": "fire"},
    {"question": "What skill does the knife represent?", "answer": "fletching", "type": "skills", "keyword": "knife"},
    {"question": "What skill does the tree represent?", "answer": "woodcutting", "type": "skills", "keyword": "tree"},
    {"question": "What skill does the watercan represent?", "answer": "farming", "type": "skills", "keyword": "watercan"},
    {"question": "What skill does the wolf represent?", "answer": "summoning", "type": "skills", "keyword": "wolf"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of up?", "answer": "down", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of up"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of left?", "answer": "right", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of left"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of right?", "answer": "left", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of right"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of down?", "answer": "up", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of down"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of black?", "answer": "white", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of black"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of white?", "answer": "black", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of white"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of cold?", "answer": "hot", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of cold"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of hot?", "answer": "cold", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of hot"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of fast?", "answer": "slow", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of fast"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of slow?", "answer": "fast", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of slow"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of good?", "answer": "bad", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of good"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of bad?", "answer": "good", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of bad"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of big?", "answer": "small", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of big"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of small?", "answer": "big", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of small"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of tall?", "answer": "short", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of tall"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of short?", "answer": "tall", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of short"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of light?", "answer": "dark", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of light"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of dark?", "answer": "light", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of dark"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of heavy?", "answer": "light", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of heavy"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of light?", "answer": "heavy", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of light"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of old?", "answer": "new", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of old"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of new?", "answer": "old", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of new"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of young?", "answer": "old", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of young"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of old?", "answer": "young", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of old"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of wet?", "answer": "dry", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of wet"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of dry?", "answer": "wet", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of dry"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of clean?", "answer": "dirty", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of clean"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of dirty?", "answer": "clean", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of dirty"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of happy?", "answer": "sad", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of happy"},
    {"question": "What is the opposite of sad?", "answer": "happy", "type": "logic", "keyword": "opposite of sad"}
  ]
}
